bayofblog.com 2016-04-07

# Privacy Policy

Bayofblog.com owns and operates this website. We are committed to the privacy and security of our visitors’ information. The following is a statement of our privacy practices:

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/ Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track user activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, bayofblog.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Information Collected**

Your personal information is not required to visit bayofblog.com

Any personal information collected is knowingly provided by you and only when requested/required during account registration for interactive participation on bayofblog.com  and during the ordering process

**Traffic Data**

Your IP address is a numeric address assigned to your computer, assigned by your Internet service provider. We automatically collect your IP address as traffic data so that we can send information back to you when requested. This is not used to identify your personal information.

Referrers are references to the web address you linked from and is automatically passed along by your web browser. We collect referrers your browser sends as part of traffic data. This is not attached to personally identifiable information.

System information such as your operating system/platform, and the type of web browser you use. This is not attached to personally identifiable information.

**Account Information**

Your information is maintained on a secure web server in what we believe to be a well protected environment.

Bayofblog.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our visitors to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Security**

This website takes every precaution to protect our visitors’ information. When visitors submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

We do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our customers’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, in a locked facility.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement** The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of bayofblog.com  then you may contact us.
